YMCA ARMED SERVICES DEPARTMENT:
University of Minnesota Libraries
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Mr. Crossett, 1920. (Box 40)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Mr. Davis, 1919. (Box 40)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with R. L. Ewing, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with James Forbes, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with O. F. Gardner, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Mr. Gethman, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Robert Good, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with John Hall, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Charles Hesselgrave, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Mr. Lake, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Thomas McLane, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Robert Monaghan, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Gerald Reynolds, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Francis Sayre, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Frederick Shipp, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with C. D. Silvernail, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with James Smith, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with W. A. Tener, 1920. (Box 41)
- War Historical Bureau, interview with Bishop Luther Wilson, 1920. (Box 41)
- Organization and operation of Post Exchange, report and related correspondence, 1919-1930.; 4 folders. (Box 42)
- Appendix to report and organization of the Post Exchange, 1919.; 4 folders. (Box 42)
- YMCA work, articles regarding, 1918-1919. (Box 42)
- Miscellaneous published material used in YMCA investigation, circa 1918-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 42)
- Price lists, 1918-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 42)
- Foyers du Soldat, extracts from letters, 1917-1918.; 4 folders. (Box 42)
- Foyers du Soldat, extracts from letters, 1917-1918.; 4 folders. (Box 43)
- Lettres d'un Jeune Soldat de la France, 1915. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, reports and letters, 1918-1920.; 2 folders. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, Report of the Work of the Foyer du Soldat among the French and Belgian Soldiers on the Western Front, 1917-1918. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, A. Wayne Hanson report, 1921.; 2 folders. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, reports, 1918-1922.; 2 folders. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, recreation publications, 1918.; 3 folders. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, De la Sympathie à la Fraternité d'Armes, 1919. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, D. A. Davis notes, 1919. (Box 43)
- Foyers du Soldat, correspondence, 1917-1921.; 3 folders. (Box 44)
- Foyers du Soldat, letters of William Sloan Coffin, 1917-1919. (Box 44)
- Outline of Standard Activities of the Foyers du Soldat, du Martin et du Civil, circa 1919. (Box 44)
- YMCA-AFG, history, 1920-1922.; 4 folders. (Box 44)
- YMCA-AFG, chief secretary's reports, 1922-1923.; 2 folders. (Box 44)
- The French Foyers, A. Wayne Hanson, 1922. (Box 44)
- AFG, reports of the YMCA in the army of occupation, 1919-1921.; 2 folders. (Box 44)
- AFG in Koblenz, reports, correspondence and clippings, 1919-1921; 7 folders. (Box 45)
- AFG, athletic handbooks, 1919-1921. (Box 45)
- AFG, athletic programs, 1920-1921. (Box 45)
- AFG, entertainment programs, 1919-1921. (Box 45)
- AFG, postcards, circa 1919-1921. (Box 45)
- AFG, blank forms, circa 1920. (Box 45)
- War Work school materials, 1918. (Box 45)
- AFG, entertainment scrapbooks (originals), 1919-1921.; 2 folders. (Box 46)
- AFG, entertainment scrapbook (photocopies), 1919-1921.; 14 folders. (Box 46)
- AFG materials in German, circa 1917-1920.; 2 folders. (Box 46)
- The AMAROC News, 1921. (Box 47)
- The YAMAROC, newsletter, 1922-1926.; 4 folders. (Box 47)
- The YMCA with the Czecho-Slovak Army, 1919. (Box 47)
- James Sprenger/Franklin Edmonds papers, 1917-1926.; 14 folders. (Box 47)
- The Y.O.U. Herald, 1925. (Box 47)
- AFG materials, P. Anderson collection, 1919-1925.; 17 folders. (Box 48)
- AFG materials, P. Anderson collection, 1919-1925.; 3 folders. (Box 49)
- First Annual Report of the YMCA with the AFG, 1919-1920. (Box 49)
- Prints of YMCA hut in Koblenz, 1922. (Box 49)
- History of the YMCA-AFG, 1920-1921, 1922. (Box 49)
- Final report of the leave area department - YMCA-AEF, 1919.; 7 folders. (Box 49)
- Leave area, publications, (France and Germany), 1918-1922.; 11 folders. (Box 50)
- Leave Area, publications, 1918-1922.; 16 folders. (Box 51)
- Leave areas, Robert Patterson, 1920.; 3 folders. (Box 51)
- Leave Area, publications, 1918-1919.; 9 folders. (Box 52)
- Policies regarding returning soldiers, reports, 1919-1920.; 3 folders. (Box 52)
- Committee for Allied Armies and Prisoners of War, 1917-1922.; 3 folders. (Box 52)
- Prisoner of war work, 1915-1920.; 7 folders. (Box 52)
- Prisoner of War work for Germany, 1914-1915.; 5 folders. (Box 53)
- Prisoner of war work for Austria, 1920-1921. (Box 53)
- Prisoner of war report, Olin Wannamaker, 1921.; 3 folders. (Box 53)
- Prisoner of war report, Donald Lowrie, 1920. (Box 53)
- D.A. Davis, extracts of correspondence, 1915-1918.; 3 folders. (Box 53)
- Prisoner of war report, England, undated, 1915-1919.; 5 folders. (Box 53)
- Red Cross publications on prisoners of war, 1915-1919. (Box 54)
- Prisoner of War Work, Dr. J.F. Hecker, 1917. (Box 54)
- Educational activities for war prisoners, undated.; 2 folders. (Box 54)
- Prisoner of War work, German language publications, 1914-1922.; 13 folders. (Box 54)
- Prisoner of War work, Sonntag, 1916-1919.; 4 folders. (Box 54)
- Prisoner of War work, German language news clippings, 1914-1918. (Box 54)
- Prisoner of War work, German language publications, 1916-1921.; 5 folders. (Box 55)
- Prisoner of War work, Belgian newspapers, 1918. (Box 55)
- Prisoner of War work, pamphlets in various languages, 1914-1918.; 4 folders. (Box 55)
- Prisoner of War work, miscellaneous articles, publications and reports, 1914-1918.; 3 folders. (Box 55)
- Prisoner of War work, reports to John Mott, 1917-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 55)
- Jewish Welfare Board publications, 1917-1919.; 5 folders. (Box 55)
- American Library Association War Service Committee, report, 1918. (Box 56)
- YWCA, miscellaneous publications, circa 1918.; 17 folders. (Box 56)
- YWCA War Work news periodicals, undated, 1917-1920. (Box 56)
- Salvation Army, publications, circa 1918.; 4 folders. (Box 56)
- War Camp Community Service, publications, circa 1918.; 20 folders. (Box 57)
- Prisoner of War: receipts for letters and parcels, 1918.; 4 folders. (Box 57A)
- Red Cross publication for prisoner of war, 1915-1919. (Box 57a)
- Friendship diary, 1919. (Box 57a)
- American Library Association pamphlets, 1918-1920.; 6 folders. (Box 57a)
- War Camp Community Service, publications, circa 1918.; 3 folders. (Box 58)
- Knights of Columbus, materials, 1919-1921.; 2 folders. (Box 58)
- National Catholic War Work Council, publications, circa 1918.; 2 folders. (Box 58)
- Knights of Columbus, Good of the Order, 1919.; 5 folders. (Box 58)
- Report on the Masonic Overseas Mission on.. .War Relief Work, circa 1920. (Box 58)
- World War I relations: American Bible Society, 1917. (Box 58)
- YMCA relations with American Red Cross, correspondence and reports, 1918-1920. (Box 58)
- YMCA relations with American Legion, correspondence, 1920-1929.; 3 folders. (Box 58)
- World War I relations: American Legion building, Paris, correspondence, 1928-1929. (Box 58)
- Work with the Navy, reports and publications, circa 1911-1925.; 9 folders. (Box 59)
- Miscellaneous Red Triangle materials, 1917-1921.; 9 folders. (Box 59)
- New York Herald, European edition, American Legion section, 1927. (Box 59)
- Miscellaneous Red Triangle materials, 1918-1932.; 5 folders. (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous Red Triangle publications, 1918-1920.; 17 folders. (Box 60)
- Miscellaneous Red Triangle publications, 1917-1920.; 4 folders. (Box 61)
- The Call to Arms: A Manual for Men Preparing for National Army Camps, 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: unidentified and B, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: C, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Devens, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Dix and Dodge, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Doniphan and Douglas, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Funston and Gordon, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Grant, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Humphreys-Lee, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Lewis, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Meade, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: Merritt-Pike, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: P-T, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: P-Sou, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Home camps: St-Ta, circa 1918. (Box 61)
- Army camps, miscellaneous, 1918.; 2 folders. (Box 62)
- Red Triangle League, reports and publications, 1918-1920.; 4 folders. (Box 62)
- Studies in Comradeship, 1918. (Box 62)
- Articles about war work, 1919.; 2 folders. (Box 62)
- Red Triangle comrade pamphlets, 1918. (Box 62)
- Y Overseas Union, reports and publications, 1920-1929. (Box 62)
- Chaplains' comments on Y service overseas, 1919.; 6 folders. (Box 62)
- Chaplains' comments on Y service overseas, 1919.; 2 folders. (Box 63)
- Chaplains, miscellaneous correspondence, clippings and reports, 1910-1920.; 4 folders. (Box 63)
- Endorsements by soldiers, 1918-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 63)
- Mothers' Day pamphlets, 1918-1920. (Box 63)
- Correspondence from J. Ross MacIver, 1917-1919. (Box 63)
- Humphrey Wilkinson letters, 1918-1919. (Box 63)
- George Hind materials, 1918-1920. (Box 63)
- Edna Perrin, letters to family, 1918-1919. (Box 63)
- Wilford Mills letters, 1918-1919. (Box 63)
- James Tappan letters, 1917-1918. (Box 63)
- F. S. Edmonds materials, History of the Intermediate Section S. O. S., 1919-1927.; 2 folders. (Box 63)
- F. S. Edmonds materials, miscellaneous clippings and publications, 1919-1935.; 9 folders. (Box 64)
- F. S. Edmonds materials, Leave Area, 1919-1931, 1957, 1962.; 8 folders. (Box 64)
- A Woman's War, Elsie Mead, undated.; 9 folders. (Box 65)
- Report of Women's Work in Wet Canteens and Rest Rooms of Paris, Helen King, 1919. (Box 65)
- AEF-YMCA Women's Work in the World War, Helen Gilchrist, undated. (Box 65)
- Women secretaries, news clippings, 1919-1921, 1970. (Box 66A)
- Women secretaries, miscellaneous publications, circa 1918. (Box 66A)
- Women secretaries, Department of the East, 1919-1920. (Box 66A)
- Women secretaries, correspondence, 1919. (Box 66A)
- Women secretaries, miscellaneous reports, 1918-1919. (Box 66A)
- Slade-Mead, correspondence, 1918-1919. (Box 66A)
- F. S. Edmonds materials, Leave Area, 1918-1920.; 4 folders. (Box 66B)
- Camp de Souge News, 1919. (Box 66B)
- Leave area materials, reunions, 1928, 1938. (Box 66B)
- Casualty and decoration lists of YMCA personnel, circa 1919. (Box 66B)
- Commendation correspondence, army of occupation, 1919. (Box 66B)
- Commendations, circa 1918.; 8 folders. (Box 66B)
- Commendations, circa 1918.; 18 folders. (Box 67)
- Commendations, circa 1918.; 16 folders. (Box 68)
- Commendations, circa 1918.; 15 folders. (Box 69)
- Commendations, circa 1918.; 9 folders. (Box 70)
- Speakers Bureau, pamphlets and resource materials, circa 1917-1918.; 3 folders. (Box 70)
- Speakers Bureau, reports, 1918. (Box 70)
- Histories, miscellaneous, 1917-1921.; 2 folders. (Box 70)
- Histories, miscellaneous, 1915-1921.; 9 folders. (Box 71)
- Histories, The Touchstone, January 1918. (Box 71)
- Histories, Harold Shock biographical, 1919.; 4 folders. (Box 71)
- Histories, Analytical Report and Syllabus of Complete Operations of the YMCA in the World War, circa 1920. (Box 71)
- Histories, American Forces in Germany, 1920.; 3 folders. (Box 71)
- Histories, Overseas Work, by Bert Pond, 1919.; 5 folders. (Box 72)
- Christian Friendship and the Man in Uniform, 1921. (Box 72)
- Y's Front, correspondence, 1939. (Box 72)
- Y's Front, George Spencer, 1939.; 5 folders. (Box 72)
- Army Influence over the YMCA in France, George Thayer, circa 1919. (Box 74)
- Building a New World, Harrison S. Elliott, 1918. (Box 74)
- A New World in the Making: Constructive Studies in the Issues of the War, Theodore Collier, 1919. (Box 74)
- With the YMCA in the First World War, Walter Spence, circa 1960. (Box 74)
- Articles on the religious aspect of the war, 1914-1918.; 6 folders. (Box 74)
- With the Indian Army in the Great War, Harold H. Peterson, 1970. (Box 74)
- Shifting Scenes in Siberia, Gail Berg Reitzel, 1918-1920. (Box 74)
- Fighting without a War, Yanks in Russia, Ralph Albertson, 1920, 1987. (Box 74)
- YMCA front line service report, E.G. Handy, 1920.; 2 folders. (Box 75)
- Bibliography of the religious significance of the war, H. H. King, 1916.; 4 folders. (Box 75)
- YMCA answer to the Inspector General, 1918-1920.; 7 folders. (Box 75)
- YMCA answer to the Inspector General, 1918-1920.; 14 folders. (Box 76)
- Letter from E. C. Carter to William Sloane, supplementing the YMCA answer to the Inspector General, 1918-1920.; 19 folders. (Box 77)
- Letter from E. C. Carter to William Sloane, supplementing the YMCA answer to the Inspector General, 1918-1920.; 18 folders. (Box 78)
- Letter from E. C. Carter to William Sloane, supplementing the YMCA answer to the Inspector General, 1918-1920.; 18 folders. (Box 79)
- Letter from E. C. Carter to William Sloane, supplementing the YMCA answer to the Inspector General, 1918-1920.; 18 folders. (Box 80)
- Reply of the International Committee of the YMCA to the additional report of the Assistant to the Inspector General, AEF, 1922.; 5 folders. (Box 81)
- Letter from E. C. Carter to William Sloane, supplementing the YMCA answer to the Inspector General (duplicate), 1918-1920.; 8 folders. (Box 81)
- Letter from E. C. Carter to William Sloane, supplementing the YMCA answer to the Inspector General (duplicate), 1918-1920.; 23 folders. (Box 82)
- Letter from E. C. Carter to William Sloane, supplementing the YMCA answer to the Inspector General (duplicate), 1918-1920.; 15 folders. (Box 83)
- Answers to criticism, circa 1919.; 16 folders. (Box 84)
- Report of the Investigation of the YMCA to the Inspector General, AEF, 1919.; 6 folders. (Box 84)
- Report of the Investigation of the YMCA to the Inspector General, AEF, 1919.; 14 folders. (Box 85)
- Report of the Investigation of the YMCA to the Inspector General, AEF (duplicate), 1919.; 4 folders. (Box 85)
- Report of the Investigation of the YMCA to the Inspector General, AEF (duplicate), 1919.; 22 folders. (Box 86)
- Samples of War Work pamphlets defending YMCA work, 1917-1919.; 4 folders. (Box 87)
- Catholic criticism of the YMCA, reports and correspondence, 1920-1921. (Box 87)
- Criticism of the YMCA, articles and correspondence, 1918-1921.; 11 folders. (Box 87)
- War work criticism, news clippings, 1918-1919.; 4 folders. (Box 87)
- Post-war investigation of the YMCA, miscellaneous F. S. Edmonds materials, undated, 1917-1939.; 19 folders. (Box 88)
- AEF-YMCA in the United Kingdom, R. L. Ewing material, 1919.; 12 folders. (Box 89)
- AEF-YMCA in the United Kingdom, R. L. Ewing materials, 1919.; 11 folders. (Box 90)
- Report to the Commander in Chief of the YMCA with the AEF, 1919.; 4 folders. (Box 90)
- Review of Inspector General's report, 1920-1922.; 4 folders. (Box 91)
- Further reply to Bradley Report, 1920. (Box 91)
- Making of Trench and Camp and Trench and Camp: Our Anniversary, 1918, undated. (Box 91)
- Trench and Camp, correspondence and reports, 1918-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 91)
- Red Triangle League Bulletin, 1920-1921. (Box 91)
- The Dauphine Doughboy, January-April 1919.; 2 folders. (Box 91)
- Dots and Dashes, YMCA at Camp Vail, NJ, (photocopies), 1918. (Box 91)
- Billy's Hut, Katherine Mayo, 1920. (Box 91)
- Books in Camp, Trench and Hospital, Library Journal, 1917. (Box 91)
- Four Months in France, Paul Kellogg, circa 1920. (Box 91)
- Mexican border work, publications and clippings, 1916-1917. (Box 91)
- Mexican border work, miscellaneous press materials, 1916.; 5 folders. (Box 91)
- War work clippings, Mexican border work, 1916-1917.; 7 folders. (Box 92)
- Mexican border work, maps (photocopies), circa 1917. (Box 92)
- The United States Army Young Men's Christian Association, graduation thesis by Charles Crissey, 1917.; 4 folders. (Box 92)
  Can also be found in Y.USA.4-3.
- Medical Training Camp: Fort Oglethorpe, Georgia, 1917. (Box 92)
- Second Report of the Provost Marshal General to the Secretary of War on the Operations of the Selective Service System to December 20, 1918, 1919. (Box 92)
- American Expeditionary Forces University, catalogue, 1919. (Box 92)
- American Expeditionary Forces University, register, 1919. (Box 92)
- Orders, reports and clippings regarding U.S. government orders and regulations, 1918-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 93)
- U.S. military, publications, 1919-1926; 4 folders. (Box 93)
- U.S. government, publications on WW I, 1917-1918.; 7 folders. (Box 93)
- U.S. government, publications on WW I, 1918-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 94)
- U.S. government, publications on WW I, 1918-1920.; 4 folders. (Box 95)
- War Department, publications, 1918-1919.; 19 folders. (Box 94)
- Enlisted men's Bible and Prayer League calendar, 1913. (Box 94)
- U.S. government report on reparations, 1924. (Box 95)
- U.S. government materials on morals and morale, 1917-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 95)
- Commission on Training Camp Activities, minutes, 1917-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 95)
- Commission on Training Camp Activities, Athletic Division, bulletin, 1918. (Box 95)
- Commission on Training Camp Activities, Athletic Division, bulletin, 1918.; 3 folders. (Box 96)
- Commission on Training Camp Activities, miscellaneous documents, 1917-1918. (Box 96)
- AEF, soldiers' letter envelopes, undated. (Box 96)
- U.S. government, foreign exchange publications, 1918. (Box 96)
- U.S. government, field service scales of rations publications, 1919. (Box 96)
- U.S. government, miscellaneous publications, 1917-1919. (Box 96)
- Navy Chaplain's manual, 1918. (Box 96)
- Soldiers and sailors bulletin, 1920. (Box 96)
- Contributions of black soldiers, pamphlets, 1918. (Box 96)
- War Department, military intelligence, correspondence with John Mott, 1918-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 96)
- War Department, Secretary of War, correspondence, 1919. (Box 96)
- War Department, transfer of welfare work to government, 1919.; 2 folders (Box 96)
- War Department, draft law correspondence and reports, 1917-1918.; 3 folders. (Box 96)
- Religious pamphlets, 1917-1920.; 3 folders. (Box 97)
- War Department, publications on international law, 1918. (Box 97)
- War Department, military training camp for business and professional men, 1915. (Box 97)
- Navy Department, correspondence, 1917. (Box 97)
- Navy Department, memoranda, 1918.; 2 folders. (Box 97)
- War Department, work reports, 1914-1921. (Box 97)
- New York Times, clippings on the military situation, 1914.; 2 folders. (Box 97)
- Pocket bibles, 1918.; 7 folders. (Box 97)
- Readings from the Holy Scriptures for Jewish Soldiers and Sailors, 1918. (Box 98)
- Enlisted men's bible and prayer league calendars, 1914-1917.; 5 folders. (Box 98)
- List of literature handled by Religious Work Department in Paris, 1918. (Box 98)
- The Leadership of Red Triangle Groups, Harrison Elliott, 1918. (Box 98)
- Religious pamphlets, 1914-1920.; 7 folders. (Box 98)
- Articles regarding the YMCA in World War I, 1918-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 99)
- Religious pamphlets, 1917-1920.; 16 folders. (Box 99)
- Religious pamphlets, 1917-1919.; 19 folders. (Box 99A)
- Articles regarding the YMCA in World War I, 1918-1919.; 8 folders. (Box 100)
- Stars and Stripes (photocopies), 1919. (Box 100)
- New York Herald (photocopies), 1919.; 2 folders. (Box 100)
- Chicago Tribune, Paris Edition (photocopies), 1919.; 2 folders. (Box 100)
- Press releases regarding YMCA in World War I, 1918-1919. (Box 100)
- Home Sector, September 27, 1919 - April 17, 1920.; 22 folders. (Box 101)
- American Legion Weekly, July 4, 1919 - March 26, 1920.; 37 folders. (Box 102)
- American Legion Weekly, August 6, 1920 - September 23, 1921.; 44 folders. (Box 103)
- Leave Area Edition, 1919. (Box 103)
- The Eaglet, 1918-1919.; 6 folders. (Box 103)
- Miscellaneous newspapers, 1919-1920.; 3 folders. (Box 103)
- Contracts, Ab-Dy, set 1, 1917-1919.; 15 folders. (Box 104)
  Contracts were originally in bound volumes; there were multiple volumes for each letter of the alphabet. The volumes are referred to as "sets" in the folder titles.
- Contracts, A-Dl, set 2, 1917-1919.; 8 folders. (Box 104)
- Contracts, Do-G, set 2, 1917-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 105)
- Contracts, Ab-Dy, set 3, 1917-1919.; 13 folders. (Box 105)
- Contracts, A-Du, set 4, 1917-1919.; 10 folders. (Box 106)
- Contracts, A-Bri, set 5, 1917-1919.; 5 folders. (Box 106)
- Contracts, Bro-Dy, set 5, 1917-1919.; 7 folders. (Box 107)
- Contracts, A-D, set 6, 1917-1919.; 4 folders. (Box 107)
- Contracts, Ea-He, set 1, 1917-1919.; 9 folders. (Box 107)
- Contracts, Hi-Ky, set 1, 1917-1919.; 5 folders. (Box 108)
- Contracts, E-K, set 2, 1917-1919.; 13 folders. (Box 108)
- Contracts, E-Ku, set 3, 1917-1919.; 7 folders. (Box 109)
- Contracts, E-Haz, set 4, 1917-1919.; 6 folders. (Box 109)
- Contracts, He-Ku, set 4, 1917-1919.; 6 folders. (Box 110)
- Contracts, E-K, set 5, 1917-1919.; 5 folders. (Box 110)
- Contracts, Ha-J, set 6, 1917-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 110)
- Contracts, La-Ne, set 1, 1917-1919.; 15 folders. (Box 111)
- Contracts, Oa-Ow, set 1, 1917-1919.; 2 folders. (Box 112)
- Contracts, Ka-Ny, set 2, 1917-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 112)
- Contracts, La-Mo, set 3, 1917-1919.; 7 folders. (Box 112)
- Contracts, Mie-Mit, set 2, 1917-1919. (Box 112)
- Contracts, Mu-Ry, set 3, 1917-1919.; 7 folders. (Box 113)
- Contracts, L-Pe, set 4, 1917-1919.; 8 folders. (Box 113)
- Contracts, Ph-Ru, set 4, 1917-1919.; 3 folders. (Box 114)
- Contracts, P-Y, set 5, 1917-1919.; 8 folders. (Box 114)
- Contracts, Pac-Pu, set 6, 1917-1919.; 6 folders. (Box 114)
- Contracts, Q-Ston, set 6, 1917-1919.; 19 folders. (Box 115)
- Contracts, Sma-Was, set 6, 1917-1919.; 16 folders. (Box 116)
- Contracts, Sha-Z, set 6, 1917-1919.; 13 folders. (Box 117)
- Contracts, St.-Ty, set 7, 1917-1919.; 6 folders. (Box 117)
- Contracts, U-Z, set 7, 1917-1919.; 5 folders. (Box 118)
- Contracts, Transport Secretaries, 1917-1919.; 4 folders. (Box 118)
- Contracts, speakers, 1917-1919. (Box 118)
- Contracts, Brotherhood of St. Andrew secretaries, 1917-1919. (Box 118)
- Contracts, incomplete, 1917-1919. (Box 118)
- Contracts, sample binding, undated. (Box 118)
- Returning secretaries, blank forms, undated. (Box 118)
- Statements of returning secretaries, A-Ar, 1918-1921.; 5 folders. (Box 118)
- Statements of returning secretaries, As-Burz, 1918-1921.; 19 folders. (Box 119)
- Statements of returning secretaries, Bil-Cla, 1918-1921.; 17 folders. (Box 120)
- Statements of returning secretaries, Cle-Em, 1918-1921.; 19 folders. (Box 121)
- Statements of returning secretaries, En-Han, 1918-1921.; 18 folders. (Box 122)
- Statements of returning secretaries, Harb-Johnson, 1918-1921.; 16 folders. (Box 123)
- Statements of returning secretaries, Johnston-McC, 1918-1921.; 17 folders. (Box 124)
- Statements of returning secretaries, McD-Nix, 1918-1921.; 17 folders. (Box 125)
- Statements of returning secretaries, No-Rosi, 1918-1921.; 19 folders. (Box 126)
- Statements of returning secretaries, Ross-Sto, 1918-1921.; 18 folders. (Box 127)
- Statements of returning secretaries, Str-Wight, 1918-1921.; 20 folders. (Box 128)
- Statements of returning secretaries, Williams-Zw, 1918-1921.; 10 folders. (Box 129)
- Statements of returning secretaries, sample binder, undated. (Box 129)
- The Rising Sun and miscellaneous newspapers, 1918-1920.; 7 folders. (Box 129)
- Disposition of World War I records, correspondence, 1928-1944.; 3 folders. (Box 129)
- United War Work Campaign, financial reports, 1917-1919. (Box 130)
- War Work Training School, Stanford "Y" Record, 1918. (Box 130)
- Leave Area materials, 1919-1926. (Box 130)
- Egyptian Expeditionary Forces, report on YMCA work with, 1918. (Box 130)